proarticlesdaily.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy - ProArticlesDaily.com

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you [register](http://proarticlesdaily.com/privacy-policy/# "Click to Continue > by InstantSavings") on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or [fill out](http://proarticlesdaily.com/privacy-policy/# "Click to Continue > by InstantSavings") a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network ******privacy** ******policy**..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To administer a contest, promotion, [survey](http://proarticlesdaily.com/privacy-policy/# "Click to Continue > by InstantSavings") or other site feature

• To send periodic emails

> [The email](http://proarticlesdaily.com/privacy-policy/# "Click to Continue > by InstantSavings") address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our [Payment gateway](http://proarticlesdaily.com/privacy-policy/# "Click to Continue > by InstantSavings") providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, [social security](http://proarticlesdaily.com/privacy-policy/# "Click to Continue > by InstantSavings") numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent ******privacy** policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online** **** **Privacy** Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your **privacy** we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online **Privacy** Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online **Privacy** Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Childrens Online** **** **Privacy** Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online **Privacy** Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online** **** **Privacy** ******Policy** Only

This online **privacy** **policy** applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

We take your **privacy** seriously. This **policy** describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. (This **privacy** **policy** is applicable to websites falling under the primary holder fill in your website(s) and urls here.)

Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets me know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own ******privacy** policies.

Controlling Your **Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have **privacy** concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own **privacy** policies.

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network ******privacy** ******policy**. (Link this to: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>)

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites ******privacy** ******policy**.

**Changes to our** **** **Privacy** ******Policy**

If we decide to change our ******privacy** ******policy** , we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the ******Privacy** ******Policy** modification date below.

This ******policy** was last modified on 08/05/2010
